<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Uzbek Cuisine</string>

    <string name="title1">Wedding Pilaf (Plov)</string>
    <string name="description1">A delightful mixture of rice, bits of meat, grated carrots and
        onions, and raisins (with a clove of roasted garlic on top). The “wedding” part refers to
        the fact that it’s easy to cook in large quantities (traditionally in a kazan over an open
        fire) and is often served on special occasions, like weddings.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription1">\tPlov is the symbol of Uzbek food. It is prepared in every
        Uzbekistan family, whether Uzbek, Russian, Tatar of Korean. Uzbek plov is the part of
        mentality of Uzbekistan people. Traditionally plov is cooked by men.\n\n\tThere are over a
        thousand of recipes of cooking Uzbek plov with various ingredients and even there are some
        cook books dedicated only to this dish.\n\n\tIn various regions of Uzbekistan, people have
        their own recipes of Uzbek plov preparation. For instance, Bukharan people prepare plov with
        green gram. Samarkand plov is light, Fergana plov is brown on the contrary. In Samarkand
        people put meat, carrot, rice in layers and steam it. In Tashkent plov all ingredients are
        roasted at the beginning.\n\n\tCommonly Uzbek plov is cooked with rice, fresh mutton or
        beef, yellow or red carrot, onions and vegetable oil. Traditionally, Uzbek plov is prepared
        in a deep cast-iron pot (kazan), which is uniformly warmed and a dish is not burnt.</string>
    <string name="ingredients1">- 3 cups long grain rice.\n- 1 kg lamb shoulder, cubed.\n- 8 Tbsp
        vegetable oil.\n- 3 medium onions.\n- 1 head of garlic, whole.\n- 1kg carrots
        (yellow if possible).\n- 1 Tbsp coriander, ground.\n- 1 Tbsp paprika.\n- 1 tsp black pepper,
        ground.\n- 4 cloves.\n- 1 tsp cumin, ground.\n- 1 cup of raisins.\n- 1 cup barberries /
        zereshk (opt.).\n- Salt.\n- 3 Tbsp wild black cumin.</string>
    <string name="methods1">1. Place the rice in a bowl and cover with water.\n\n2. Heat a large
        pot. Pour in the oil and add the lamb. Cook on high heat until the meat browns.\n\n3. Cut
        the onions in four and add them to the meat with the head of garlic. Mix and cook for 5
        minutes.\n\n4. Add the spices and enough water to cover the meat and the onions. Cook for
        another 15 minutes.\n\n5. Meanwhile, peel and cut the carrots lengthwise.\n\n\6. Place the
        carrots on the meat. Strain the rice and add it to the pot. Add enough boiling water to
        cover the rice. Shake the pot gently in order to spread the rice evenly.\n\n7. Bring to a
        boil. Sprinkle the raisins, barberries, black cumin and salt into the pot. Cook another 5
        minutes.\n\n8. Reduce the heat to low, cover and cook for another 20 minutes.\n\n9. Garnish
        with pomegranate if you wish. Serve with a tomato and green onion salad.</string>


    <string name="title2">Manty</string>
    <string name="description2">Steamed dumplings sprinkled with dill and served with sour cream.
        Meat, spices, or vegetables can make up the stuffing, so you never know what you’re going
        to get!</string>
    <string name="fullDescription2">\tOnly the Uzbek people could preserve the age-old recipe of
        classical uzbek manti and offered an alternative to the Chinese bamboo lattices, on which
        dumplings were cooked. Yes, this tableware, called manti-kozon (cauldron for manti) or
        "mantyshnitsa" was born in Uzbekistan.\n\n\tUzbek manti is one of the many dishes of Uzbek
        cuisine, which gives scope for the irrepressible imagination of cooks. Only the composition
        of the dough is in fact unchanged, and stuffing safely varies depending on the season and
        taste preferences. So, stuffing can consist of meat, potatoes, greens, turnips, tomato,
        sweet pepper, and even there is manti with pumpkin. The main thing, that onion and dumba
        (fatty tail) would be always on hand in abundance.\n\n\tHowever, the recipe of uzbek manti,
        assuming a part of minced meat, onions and fatty tail is really the most favorite,
        widespread and commonly used.\n\n\tUzbek manti with mutton and onions is a holiday not only
        for the stomach, is a feast for the soul! A large dish of flavored envelopes of the finest
        dough in the middle of the table, the noise and hubbub, sour cream, bowls with hot tea and
        arms, stretching for a new portion of Uzbek manti.</string>
    <string name="ingredients2">- Flour - 500 g.\n- Eggs - 2 pcs.\n- Boiled water - 150 -170 ml.\n-
        Salt - 15 g.\n- For the stuffing: Lamb of average fat content (back or thigh) - 600 gr.\n-
        Fat tail - 100 gr.\n- Onions - 600 g.\n- Salt - 20 g.\n- Ground black pepper - 10 gr.\n-
        Ground zira (cumin) - 5 gr.</string>
    <string name="methods2">1. Knead the dough, as well as for other flour Uzbek dishes, let the
        dough "lie down", after covering it.\n\n2. Half a piece of the dough should be rolled out in
        a large thin sheet, trying to give it a square shape to reduce the number of substandard
        scraps.\n\n3. The rolled out layer we put in the form of an accordion so as to obtain a
        rectangle of 4 layers. Cut the folded dough into equal squares. As a result, we obtain four
        long strips of equal width, about 9–10 centimeters.\n\n4. Repeat all manipulations with the
        second half of the dough. Impose strips on each other and we share them into equal neat
        squares.\n\n5. Now you can start sculpting of Uzbek manti. In the middle of a square of each
        piece of dough we spread the stuffing, potatoes, and then a few pieces of fat. Put together
        the opposite corners of the square. Then, pinch together the edges.\n\n6. The ready manti are
        spread on a sheet of mantovarka (cauldron for manti) greased with oil.\n\n7. Before direct
        cooking of Uzbek manti, you should fill the bottom pan of cauldron with water and put it on
        the fire to make it boil.\n\n8. Uzbek manti should be stewed approximately 45 minutes.\n\n9.
        The result, delicious and very juicy real Uzbek manti, which will be appreciated at true
        worth.</string>

    <string name="title3">Lagman Soup</string>
    <string name="description3">Something of a Central Asian version of ramen, this is a spicy,
        meaty broth filled with chunks of lamb, handspun noodles, and vegetables. It also comes in
        a non-soup version.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription3">\tAlong with pilaf and shashlik, Uzbek lagman is considered one
        of the main national dishes of Uzbekistan. This fragrant Uigur, according to other sources,
        Dungan dish won the recognition of the majority of the Central Asian peoples and Uzbek
        talented chefs added its own original ingredients.\n\n\tThe name "Lagman" is derived from
        the word "lyumyan" translated from Dungan to "stretch the dough." It reflects the main
        feature of cooking lagman: homemade dough for noodles, which is put in the soup, specially
        rolled and hand-drawn.\n\n\tUzbek lagman is very famous and popular dish of Uzbek cuisine.
        Lagman Uzbek noodles is cooked from meat (especially lamb), various vegetables
        (green radish, onion, carrot, bell pepper, etc.) and special long noodles.</string>
    <string name="ingredients3">- 2 tablespoons olive oil.\n- 1 onion, finely chopped.\n- ½ pound
        beef chuck, cut into strips.\n- 1 teaspoon ground cumin.\n- ½ teaspoon ground black pepper.
        \n- 2 tablespoons tomato paste.\n- 1 carrot, cut into thin strips.\n- 1 green bell pepper,
        cut into 1-inch strips.\n- 3 small potatoes, cubed.\n- ½ cup thinly sliced celery.\n- 8 cups
        water.\n- 2 teaspoons salt.\n- ½ cup finely chopped parsley.\n- 3 large cloves garlic,
        minced.\n- 2 (8 ounce) packages thin Chinese noodles.</string>
    <string name="methods3">1. Heat oil in a large pot over high heat. Reduce heat to medium-high;
        cook and stir onion in the hot oil until golden, 3 to 5 minutes. Stir in beef strips, cumin,
        and black pepper; cook until beef is browned, about 5 minutes. Stir in tomato paste and cook
        for 2 to 3 minutes.\n\n2. Stir carrot into the pot; cook until coated with tomato paste, 2 to
        3 minutes. Add green bell pepper; cook for 1 minute. Add potatoes and celery; cook for 5
        minutes. Pour in water; bring to a boil. Season water with salt. Reduce heat to low and
        simmer soup until potatoes are soft, about 40 minutes.\n\n3. Stir parsley and garlic into
        the soup. Simmer until garlic is soft, 10 to 15 minutes.\n\n4. Bring a large pot of lightly
        salted water to a boil. Cook noodles in the boiling water, stirring occasionally, until
        tender yet firm to the bite, 3 to 5 minutes. Rinse and drain well. Divide among serving
        bowls. Ladle hot soup over noodles.</string>

    <string name="title4">Chuchvara Soup</string>
    <string name="description4">A soup in which small dumplings are boiled in salt water or bouillon
        and served with sour milk (“suzma”) and seasoned with pepper, onion, tomato paste,
        black pepper, and sour cream.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription4">\tYou can puzzle for a long time, but never guess what is
        hidden behind such a mysterious name. And chuchvara are fragrant and juicy Uzbek dumplings.
        They differ from the products so familiar to us in their shape and miniature size.
        The serving is also different - they are served floating in a fragrant broth!\n\n\t
    There is nothing tastier and more fragrant than the incomparable homemade chuchvara!
        You will have to tinker with it a little, small dumplings require painstaking work
        in sculpting them. But the result will make you immediately forget about all the efforts
        expended, the food is so tasty.</string>
    <string name="ingredients4">For the dough:\n- 100g water\n- 1/2 Tbs. salt\n- 1 large egg
        \n- 80-110g all purpose flour\nFor the filling:\n- 250g ground meat (lamb or beef)
        \n- 2 onions peeled and finely diced\n- Salt and pepper\n- 5 Tbs. butter
        \n- 4 Tbs. lamb’s tail fat cut into tiny cubes (optional)\n Cayenne pepper
        (for 1 lucky dumpling)\nFor serving:\n- Sour cream or yogurt\n- 2 Tbs. chopped cilantro
    </string>
    <string name="methods4">1. For the dough: Combine all the dough ingredients in a medium bowl,
        adding the flour bit by bit as needed. Knead to form a moderately firm dough. Cover and
        let dough rest for 15 min.\n\n2. For the filling: Sauté the onions over medium heat in the
        butter until golden brown. Add the meat and lamb fat, if using, then season generously
        with salt and pepper. Cook until meat is no longer pink. Set aside to cool.
        \n\n3. To assemble: Roll out the dough on a floured surface into a large rectangle,
        1/16″ thick (or as thin as you can get it.)\n\n4. Cut the dough into 1.5 x 1.5 inch squares.
    \n\n5. Put 1/2-1 tsp. of filling in the middle of each square. Fold the dough corner to corner
        (making a triangle), pinching the edges together to seal. Pinch two corners together
        (like a hug!) Continue making chuchvara in the same way until you’re out of filling.
    \n\n6. To serve: Chuchvara can be frozen at this point! Or cook in salted boiling water for 3-5
        minutes until pasta is translucent and tender. Serve Chuchvara with some of the cooking
        liquid (called soup) ladled into a serving dish. Dollop with plain yogurt or sour cream
        and sprinkle with chopped cilantro.\n\n7. Alternatively, chuchvara can be served
        “without soup” and topped with fried onions and diced fresh tomatoes. Enjoy!
        (I hope you get the lucky spicy one!)</string>

    <string name="title5">Samsa</string>
    <string name="description5">A triangular dough pastry that’s baked in a tandoor oven so that
        the bread is somehow both crunchy and super-soft. Like manty, they can be filled with a
        variety of things, including ground lamb, herbs, and, the most interesting
        traditional option, pumpkin.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription5">Samsa (also spelled samsa, somsa, samoosa, sambosak, sambusa,
        singada, samuza, somasi, somas) is an Uzbek food consisting of flaky pasties with various
        fillings, both served at ceremonies and eaten in an everyday life. Samsa may have different
        shapes and forms and be cooked in a multiplicity of ways.\n\n\tToday’s Samsa is usually
        filled with meat (mutton, chicken or beef), vegetables (pumpkin, potato or onion),
        mushrooms, eggs, peas, herbs or even sweet substances. However, as in most of the Uzbek
        dishes, it is the spices, such as zira (zra, kumin), black and red hot pepper, and sesame
        (covering Samsa on the top), that make the taste of the pasties really unique.\n\n\tIn the 
        former times Samsa was cooked only in a tandir oven (a Central Asian clay oven, also 
        spelled tandyr, tandoor), on coals. Samsa baked in a tandir has specific taste and flavour 
        and is filled with small pieces of meat, onion and some amount of fat from a sheep’s tail. 
        Nowadays, some sorts of Samsa are cooked in gas or electric ovens, which is faster and 
        more convenient and, at the same time, makes Samsa retain its original qualities.</string>
    <string name="ingredients5">For the Pastry Cover:\n- 2 C AP Flour Unbleached\n- 1 C Warm Water
        As Needed\n- 1/2 Tsp Salt\n- 1 Tbsp Ghee Clarified Butter\nFor Filling:\n- 1 lb Minced lamb
        Not extra lean 15- 30% fat\n- 3 Medium Onions Finely chopped\n- 1 Tsp Salt\n- 1 Tsp Fresh
        Ground Pepper\n- 1 Tsp Cumin Seeds Lightly crushed\n- 2 Tbsp Mint Leaves Chopped finely\n-
    1 Tsp Minced Garlic\nOther Ingredients:\n- 1/4 C Ghee More if needed\n- 1 Egg For Egg Wash</string>
    <string name="methods5">Make the Dough:\n1. Heat the water to warm. Mix the flour and salt
        together. Add the ghee and knead using warm water (stand mixer about 4 to 5 minutes).
        The dough should be soft and very pliable. Form into a ball, cover and set aside to rest
        for 20 minutes  to 1  hour.\n2. Divide the dough into at least 3 equal portions.\n3.
        Lightly dust a work surface and roll out one portion of  the  dough  into a thin rectangle
        (2 to 3 mm thickness).\n4. Generously spread some  ghee  all over the rectangle with a
        spoon orr pastry brush.\n5. Roll out the next portion of dough into a similar rectangle.
        Place it on top of the first rectangle. Brush liberally with ghee and repeat the process
        with the remaining portion(s).\n6. Roll the  stacked rectangle starting at  the longer edge
        to form a log. Wrap the log in a plastic wrap or parchment and chill for at least
        30 minutes.\n\nMake the filling:\n- Finely chop the onions. Take 3 to 4 cups of chopped
        onions and add to the minced lamb. Add all the remaining ingredients for the filling.
        Mix everything together until uniform.\n\nShape Samsa:\n1. Remove dough from the fridge.
        Slice into about 18 to 20 equal pieces. Liberally flour the work surface. Take each
        dough disc and flatten it using your palm (or a thin rolling pin) to a circle of about
        4 inch diameter. The edges should be thinner than the center.\n2. Divide the filling into
        as many equal portions as the dough discs.\n3. Place one portion in the center of a disc.
        Imagine a triangle around the filling .Pick up two side of the imaginary triangle and
        start pinching them close to the center.\n4. Pick up the third side and close all sides
        by pinching. All three sides should meet at the center…\n\nBake:\n1. Pre heat the oven to
        375°F (190°C) with the oven rack in the center.\n2. Line a baking tray with parchment paper
        or coat with oil. Place the samsas on the tray with the seam sides facing down.\n3. Beat
        the egg with 1 tsp water to make the egg wash. Brush the tops of the samsas with the
        egg wash.\n4. Bake for about 30 minutes or until the tops are golden brown.\n5. Transfer
        to a cooling rack. Serve warm.
</string>

    <string name="title6">Naryn</string>
    <string name="description6">An oriental merchant favorite, the dish is composed of hand-spun
        noodles and boiled jerk meat, served with minced onions and black pepper. Traditionally,
        it is made with horse-meat.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription6">\tUzbek cuisine does not cease to amaze with a rich variety of
        traditional dishes, and the ingredients are mostly the same - flour, water, meat and salt.
        At the festive tables of Uzbekistan and in everyday life in the markets one can often find
        a national Uzbek dish - norin. The unusual taste of lace-like noodles in combination with
        horsemeat (classic version) makes the dish taste fantastic.\n\n\tNorin (narin) - is
        home-made noodles with horsemeat, more precisely, with kazy (horse meat sausage). However,
        recipes of norin allow using beef and mutton.\n\n\tIn Uzbekistan norin is a traditional
        dish of great festivals, cooked not only for the guests, but also for all the neighbors.
        It is a special dish for Ramazan Hait (Eid-al Fitr), when the fest begins with bustle with
        treats - from one to take, others to treat - with cold norin on a sunny flat bread, with
        hot pilaf in colored plate - kosa, or with baursak, urama, chak-chak and many others. This
        Uzbek tradition symbolizes peace, friendship, prosperity and, most importantly,
        holds good-neighborly relations.</string>
    <string name="ingredients6">- Mutton (Meat) - 300 gr\n- Fat tail fat - 70 gr\n- Smoked brisket - 200 gr
\n- Flour - 2 beaker\n- Onion - 100 gr\n- Egg - 1 pcs\n- Water - 7 beaker\n- Salt\n- Pepper</string>
    <string name="methods6">1. The meat is boiled in water for 1 hour. When cooked, remove from the
        water and cool. It is then cut into small straws (kokil).\n\n2. Beat eggs in flour,
        knead medium hard dough in lukewarm water and leave to rise. The dough is spread out
        to a medium thickness and cut into rectangular bowl widths.\n\n3. These pieces are cooked
        in salted water. Once the baked dough is removed from the water, it is spread on the table
        in the heat and dried. At the same time try to spread it completely in the heat so that the
        dough does not stick to each other. The dried dough on both sides is spread on a plate in
        a uniform plane, greased between them and stacked on top of each other.\n\n4. Long strips
        are cut from the dough and cut into small pieces.\n\n5. The minced meat and dough are
        mixed with cumin.\n\n6. The dish is served with boiled meat broth in a separate bowl on
        the table.\n\nNote: Meat will be more delicious if pre-salted and seasoned.</string>

    <string name="title7">Dimlama</string>
    <string name="description7">A hearty stew made of meat, potatoes, onions, vegetables and
        sometimes fruit. And of course spices. And dill. Always dill.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription7">\tDimlama is an Uzbek stew made with various combinations of
        meat, potatoes, onions, vegetables, and sometimes fruits.\n\n\tMeat and vegetables are cut
        into large pieces and placed in layers in a tightly sealed pot to simmer slowly in their
        own juices.\n\n\tVegetables for dimlama may include, in addition to potatoes and onions,
        also carrots, cabbage, eggplants, tomatoes, sweet peppers, spiced with garlic and a
        variety of herbs and condiments.\n\n\tDimlama is usually cooked during spring and summer
        when there is a wide choice of vegetables. It is served on a large plate and eaten with
        spoon.</string>
    <string name="ingredients7">- 1/2-1 lb cubed lamb or beef\n- 1 large onion, sliced in quarter
        moons\n- 5 small yellow potatoes cut in half\n- 2-3 large carrots, peeled \u0026 sliced
        \n- 2 red peppers, sliced in strips\n- 2 large tomatoes, cut in wedges\n- 5 cloves garlic,
        quartered\n- 3 green onions, sliced\n- 1 1/2 tsp cumin seed\n- 1 small, green cabbage
        cut in hunks\n- salt \u0026 pepper, as needed</string>
    <string name="methods7">1. First, let’s brown the lamb and onion in oil. You want to get it
        really good and toasty, as that’s the main source of dimlama’s flavor.\n\n2. Next, layer on
        the veggies, being sure to season with salt and pepper as you go.\n\n3. First, the potatoes,
        carrots, and peppers.\n\n4. Next, the tomatoes, garlic, green onion, and cumin seed.\n\n5.
    Finally, the cabbage. You’ll want to cut the cabbage in large wedges, then peel off the outer
        leaves to cover any gaps along the surface of the dimlama.\n\n6. Cover tightly and simmer
        gently until all the vegetables are tender. Do not stir! Some recipes say 1 1/2 hours,
        but I found mine took closer to 2 1/2 hours. The cabbage takes the longest, so use that
        as your indicator of doneness. Garnish with fresh cilantro, as desired.\n\n\tEnjoy with a
        smile, a friend, and happy conversation!\n\n\tWhile you eat, pay attention to all those
        amazing layers of flavor, perhaps while looking at an entirely different sort of layering.</string>


    <string name="title8">Kebab (Shaslik)</string>
    <string name="description8">Chunks of lamb, chicken, or lyulya (a mix of mutton and spices)
        served on steel skewers and topped with more slices of raw onion than you ever thought
        you’d encounter. It’s often served with Adjika- a bright red, spicy sauce made from hot
        red peppers.</string>
    <string name="fullDescription8">\tThere are disputes about where shashlik was first come up
        with and how to translate this dish. Here are some of the most plausible versions
        of the origin of shashlik.\n\n\t“Shash” from with ancient Turkic means “piece”. And ”lik”
        means ”six”. As a result, shashlik - is six pieces of meat.\n\n\tUzbek shashlik, is mostly
        cooked this way. Pieces are of different sizes. It depends on the brazier.
        But the pieces are always six.\n\n\tAs with other national dishes, each region of Uzbekistan
        offers its variants of preparation of this dish, and all regions do it exceptionally good.
        But the championship is rightfully Gijduvon shashlik. Gijduvon - a small district center,
        located near Bukhara . Gijduvon shashlik prepared here, is considered the best and unique.
        It is impossible to understand the secret of making Gijduvon shashlik, but the taste it has
        is very special and memorable. It is noted by all the people who tried it at least once.
        \n\n\tThe most popular Uzbek shashliks are lamb, beef and chicken shashliks. There are many
        variants, as the technology of preparations, and in shape, size and choice of meat portions.
        And there are Uzbek shashliks, surrounded by mysteries.</string>
    <string name="ingredients8">- 1 pound lamb, leg or shoulder, trimmed of all fat, cut into
        2-inch cubes.\n- 1/2 cup olive oil.\n- 1/2 cup lemon juice.\n- 1 teaspoon freshly ground
        black pepper.\n- 1 teaspoon salt\n- 1/4 teaspoon ground red pepper (like cayenne).
        \n- 2 medium onions, cut into eighths.\n- 1 pint cherry tomatoes.\n- 2 large green peppers,
        cut into 1-inch chunks.</string>
    <string name="methods8">1. Gather the ingredients.\n\n2. In a bowl, combine the lamb, olive oil,
        lemon juice, pepper, salt, and red pepper. Allow to marinate in the refrigeratorfor at least
        2 to 3 hours prior to cooking.\n\n3. Apply a light coat of oil onto each skewer prior to
        threading the meat. Place the marinated meat onto the skewers (about 6 cubes per skewer).
    \n\n4. Place the vegetables on separate skewers, alternating the type of vegetable.
        \n\n5. Place the lamb shashlik skewers on the grill or under the broiler and cook for
        10 to 12 minutes, or until the meat reaches your desired doneness.
        Rotate the skewers to ensure even cooking.\n\n6. Add the vegetable skewers to the grill
        during the last 5 minutes of cooking time. Turn every so often to cook all sides.
        The vegetables should be crisp, yet tender. Be careful not to overcook.\n\n7. Serve the lamb
        and vegetables on the skewers, or remove the meat and veg and place them on a serving
        platter.\n\n8. Enjoy.</string>

    <string name="title9">Shurpa</string>
    <string name="description9">A soup made out of fatty meat (usually mutton) and fresh garden
        vegetables like tomato, carrot, and slices onions. There are two version: Kaytnama
        (made from fresh meat) and Kovurma (made from fried meat).</string>
    <string name="fullDescription9">\tThis rich lamb and vegetable soup, also known as Shurpa
        is a well-known dish in Uzbekistan. Simple to make, this one is sure to become a
        favorite you’ll make over and over again!\n\n\tIn Uzbekistan, Shurpa often is served with
        samsa, and as popular as pilaf and shish kebab leading its way to the tables on all holidays
        and events as well as weeknight family gatherings.\n\n\tThis soup requires some patience and
        high-quality ingredients. Not the kind of soup you can cook from scraps. Ask your butcher
        for a good quality lamb on a bone, preferably ribs. I used a rack of lamb and my broth
        turned out phenomenally rich and hearty. Lots of onions, flashy red bell peppers, ripe and
        sweet tomatoes, fresh and fragrant herbs. Slowly simmer everything in a pot and in a few
        hours you will be rewarded with the most delicious Uzbek Shurpa Soup.</string>
    <string name="ingredients9">- 1-2 lb lamb ribs.\n- 3 medium yellow onions, sliced.\n- 2 medium
        carrots, roughly chopped.\n- 3 medium potatoes, halfed.\n- 1 red bell pepper, sliced.
        \n- 1 chili pepper, sliced.\n- 2 medium tomatoes, roughly chopped.\n- salt and black pepper
        to taste.\n- 1 tbsp coriander powder.\n- 1 tsp cumin powder.\n- 1 tbsp dried basil.\n- ⅓
        cup cilantro, chopped.\n- 1 sweet onion, sliced.\n- 2 tbsp lemon juice.\n- 1 tbsp sugar.
        \n- 1 tbsp oil</string>
    <string name="methods9">1. Season lamb with salt and pepper. Heat the oil in Dutch oven over
        high heat and brown meat on all sides, about 5 minutes.\n\n2. Cover the meat with water
        and bring to a boil. Skim off any foam that comes up.\n\n3. Reduce the heat to low and cook
        partially covered for 30 minutes.\n\n4. Add carrots and onions to the soup and cook
        for 20 minutes longer.\n\n5. While the soup is cooking, combine sliced sweet onion with
        sugar and lemon juice in a small bowl. Set aside to marinate.\n\n6. Add potatoes, spices,
        salt and pepper to the pot and simmer until potatoes are almost cooked through,
        about 10 minutes.\n\n7. Add peppers and tomatoes and cook for another 10 minutes.
        \n\n8. Add marinated onion and its juices to the soup and cook for a few more minutes.
        \n\n9. Serve garnished with cilantro.</string>
    <string name="ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="method">Methods</string>
    <string name="position">position</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="text_about_app">This exciting application provides a collection of the most
        popular dishes in Uzbekistan\'s cuisine, as well as a brief description of each dish,
        a list of ingredients, and instructions on how to prepare each dish in the
        traditional Uzbek way.</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>

</resources>